mwave.com 2019-08-14

# mwave.com: Privacy & Security

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Mwave.com. If you have any questions regarding this statement, please visit our Contact Us page to reach the appropriate department. 

**We respect your privacy**  
At Mwave.com, we value our customers and their privacy. All personal information is used to ensure efficient processing of your order. This information is used by our staff for contacting and identifying customers and their needs. We will not give, sell, rent, or loan any personally identifiable information to any third party, unless we are legally required to do so or you authorize us to do so.

**No SPAMMING!**  
Unsolicited, "spam" mail is not sent to Mwave.com's customers. The only email customers will receive, are updates to their recent orders and occasional promotions, **if requested.** Customers can be removed from our promotion list at anytime, by visiting our [Unsubscribe link](http://www.mwave.com/mwave/emailunsubscribe/default.aspx?email=). Mwave.com is not responsible for information and actions by third party individuals who have received information from the customer's directly. 

**Your personal information Is Secure**  
Mwave.com uses the industry standard security protocol Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to encode sensitive information like your credit card number that passes between you and Mwave.com. We employ the latest 128-bit encryption technology in all areas of the site which require you to provide your personal or account information. This means that the credit card information you send is encrypted by your computer, and then decrypted again on our side, preventing others from accessing your private information in between. So, when using an SSL capable browser, shopping on Mwave.com's web site is perfectly safe.

If you have any questions regarding Mwave.com's privacy/security pledge, please visit our Contact Us page to reach the appropriate department.

| 

* * *

More Privacy Terms...

Mwave.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **Mwave.com.** Any changes or updates to our privacy practices will be updated through our website. 

Log Files   
We use IP addresses, browser type, time of day, to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Registration  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor in the event of a problem when processing an order. For example, problems with credit card verification, product availability, etc. Users have a choice of receiving future mailings; during the registration process. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. i.e, in the event there is a problem processing an order, corporate changes, or changes in privacy practices. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. The customer ID numbers are assigned to Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. 

Links/3rd Parties   
This site contains links to other sites. **Mwave.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. From time to time, we may present offers to you from third party partners, and we may share certain information with those third party partners. We will not share any personally identifiable information with any third party without your consent. 

Mwave.com is the sole collector of information, and is not shared with any 3rd parties without your specific consent. However, we do offer printable rebate forms and warranty information. Mwave.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of those companies. Please review their respective privacy statements. 

Security   
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. 

If you have any questions about the security at our web site, please visit our Contact Us page. 

Removal/Opt Out  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. E-mail us: Visit our Contact Us page to reach the appropriate department. 
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address: 20159 Paseo Del Prado, Walnut, CA 91789
  3. You can call the following telephone number: 1-800-234-3358 

Correct/Update  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. web site: [Update/Modify Account Information](https://www.mwave.com/mwave/secure/customerprofile.asp?)
  2. Contact Info: Visit our Contact Us page to e-mail us. 
  3. send mail to the following postal address: 20159 Paseo Del Prado, Walnut, CA 91789
  4. call the following telephone number: 1-800-234-3358 

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Mwave.com  
20159 Paseo Del Prado  
Walnut, CA 91789  
Or visit our Contact Us page to reach the appropriate department.
